bestcrosswords.com 2012-06-21

# BestCrosswords.com - BESTCROSSWORDS.COM Privacy Policy

|  | 

Welcome to BESTCROSSWORDS.COM, which is provided by PYROMOD SOFTWARE INC (either "we" or "us"). PYROMOD SOFTWARE INC knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This document describes our privacy policy. **By visiting BESTCROSSWORDS.COM, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy**. 

## TERMS OF SERVICE

Please review our Terms of Service, which also governs your visit to BESTCROSSWORDS.COM. 

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. You can review the most current version of this policy by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" hypertext link located at the bottom of our web pages. You are responsible for checking this policy periodically for changes. If you continue to use BESTCROSSWORDS.COM after we post changes to this policy, you are signifying your acceptance of the new policy. 

## INFORMATION COLLECTED

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your browsing experience at BESTCROSSWORDS.COM. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future browsing for you, improving our games, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you access BESTCROSSWORDS.COM. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * **Advertisers:** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

## INFORMATION SHARING

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * When it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * If PYROMOD SOFTWARE INC is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, PYROMOD SOFTWARE INC will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

## INFORMATION SECURITY

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to PYROMOD SOFTWARE INC employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

## DATA INTEGRITY

PYROMOD SOFTWARE INC processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

## QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us here. 

|  |   
---|---|---|---|---
